<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Facts App</string>

    <string name="kotlin">Kotlin</string>
    <string name="cpp">C++</string>
    <string name="python">Python</string>
    <string name="php">PHP</string>
    <string name="scratch">Scratch</string>
    <string name="go">Golang</string>
    <string name="js">JavaScript</string>


    <string name="kt_det">
        A multi-purpose language.
        \n Often used to develop android applications.
        \nIt is a fun and quick to adapt language</string>

    <string name="cpp_det">
        It is a powerful general-purpose programming language.
        \nIt can be used to develop operating systems, browsers, games, and so on.
       \nC++ has influenced many other programming languages, some of which include C#, Java and even newer versions of C.
        \nIf C++ was never created, who knows what these programming languages would look like today🤔.
    +</string>
    <string name="python_det">
        The language’s name isn’t about snakes, but about the popular British comedy troupe Monty Python (from the 1970s).\n
        Guido,the creator, himself is a big fan of Monty Python’s Flying Circus.
        \nBeing in a rather irreverent mood, he named the project ‘Python’. </string>
    <string name="php_det">
        PHP originally stood for Personal Home Page.
\nPHP which is now officially known as ‘Hypertext Preprocessor’ was released in the year 1995.
    </string>
    <string name="scratch_det">
Scratch is a block-based visual programming language and website targeted primarily at children.
        \nUsers of the site can create online projects using a block-like interface.
    </string>
    <string name="go_det">
       It is the language developed by Google.
        \nIt is useful for carrying out programming for scalable servers and large software systems.
        \nThe Golang programming language was built to fill in the gaps of C++ and Java that Google came across while working with its servers and distributed systems.
    </string>
    <string name="js_det">
        Along with HTML an CSS, JavaScript is one of the three main things of the www (World Wide Web).
        \nIt enables interactive web pages and thus is an essential part of web applications.
        \nA majority of websites use it and all major web browsers have a devoted JavaScript engine to execute it.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_in">Sign in or login</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome !</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Not a valid email</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="Bk_logo">Book Logo</string>
    <string name="lang_logo">Logo</string>

</resources>